<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>BJP Sweeps NMMC Elections: Opposition Crushed</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-20/bjp-nmmc-win.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The BJP dominated the 2026 NMMC elections. Turns out, people <em>do</em> like flyovers and promises of more development. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>The saffron wave crashed over Navi Mumbai. The BJP steamrolled the competition in yesterday's NMMC elections, securing a majority that even their most optimistic supporters didn't predict. Forget a close contest; this was a demolition.</p>
<p>Early results trickled in from the polling centers near Nerul's Seawoods Gr...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-20</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-20/bjp-nmmc-win.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>CISF Cyclathon: Navi Mumbai gets sweaty, eco-friendly visit</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-20/cisf-cyclathon-mumbai.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: CISF cyclists are rolling into Mumbai on February 11th as part of a massive coastal ride. Expect spandex and maybe some sore bums.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Get ready to dodge some lycra! The Central Industrial Security Force (CISF) is bringing its "Cyclathon 2026" to our fair city. We're picturing a peloton of very serious cyclists hitting the streets.</p>
<p>They're slated to arrive in Mumbai around February 11th. After battling headwinds and questionable coas...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-20</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-20/cisf-cyclathon-mumbai.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NMMC Wins Award: Property Tax Gets Digital Upgrade</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-20/nmmc-scotch-award.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: NMMC just snagged a Scotch Award for making property tax less of a headache. Seriously, anything that makes paying taxes slightly less soul-crushing is a win in our book.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>NMMC is patting itself on the back. They won the Scotch Award 2025. Why? Because they dragged property tax kicking and screaming into the 21st century.</p>
<p>Apparently, their digital reforms and governance initiatives impressed the judges. Think online portals, strea...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-20</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-20/nmmc-scotch-award.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tailor arrested in Vashi for child sexual assault.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-19/tailor-arrest-vashi.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A 43-year-old tailor in Vashi got arrested for sexually assaulting a minor. What is wrong with people?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The cops picked up a tailor from Sector 17, Vashi, yesterday, following allegations of sexual assault on a minor girl. The Times of India reported the arrest but didn't name the accused.</p>
<p>The victim's family filed the FIR at the Vashi police station. Details are sketchy, but the charges are serious. The accused is cooling his hee...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-19</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-19/tailor-arrest-vashi.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kharghar Gets Fresh: Navi Mumbai's First Agri-Centre</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-19/kharghar-agri-centre.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Kharghar just got greener with Navi Mumbai's first city-level agriculture centre. Finally, something interesting happens in Sector 34 besides traffic.</p>
</blockquote>...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-19</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-19/kharghar-agri-centre.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cop Impersonator Swindles Senior Citizen Out of ₹4 Crore</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-19/cyber-fraud-kharghar.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A 68-year-old from Kharghar lost ₹4 Crore to a cyber fraudster posing as a police officer. Honestly, who even has that kind of money just lying around?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Kharghar resident Mr. Sharma (name changed to protect his rapidly dwindling assets) received a call last Tuesday from a person claiming to be a Cyber Crime Unit officer. The fake cop informed Sharma that his bank accounts were compromised and needed "securing." </p>
<p>Sound familiar? It...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-19</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-19/cyber-fraud-kharghar.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>RCB Dominates Navi Mumbai: WPL 2026 Favorites?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-19/rcb-wpl-domination.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: RCB had a clean sweep in the Navi Mumbai leg of WPL 2026. Looks like Smriti Mandhana's squad came to win, not just participate.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Is it just us, or is the Women's Premier League actually exciting this year? RCB, written off before a single ball was bowled, just wrapped up a perfect run at the DY Patil Stadium.</p>
<p>Smriti Mandhana’s side didn't just win; they steamrolled the competition. Forget nail-biters; these were proper, convincing...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-19</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-19/rcb-wpl-domination.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>K Raheja Corp: New School Coming to Navi Mumbai</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-19/k-raheja-school.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: K Raheja Corp is building a school in Navi Mumbai. Finally, some good news that isn't about another delayed infrastructure project.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>K Raheja Corp is adding a school to its property portfolio in Navi Mumbai. No specific location was given, because <em>obviously</em>. </p>
<p>Details are scarce, but the real estate giant is expanding into education, apparently. Will it be another fancy international school charging lakhs? Place your bets ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-19</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-19/k-raheja-school.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Wipro Doubles Down on Airoli, Mindspace</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-18/wipro-airoli-expand.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Wipro just leased 1.45 lakh sq ft in Mindspace, Airoli. Looks like someone's betting big on Navi Mumbai... or just got a sweet deal.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Wipro's planting a flag – a big one – in Airoli's Mindspace. We're talking 1.45 lakh sq ft of prime office space. That's enough room to house approximately 1,500 more souls! The IT giant is clearly bullish on its Navi Mumbai operations.</p>
<p>Is this a sign of Navi Mumbai's continued rise as an IT hub? Or...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-18</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-18/wipro-airoli-expand.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BJP Back in Power After Decade-Long NMMC Hiatus</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-18/bjp-nmmc-win.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: BJP snagged 66 seats in the NMMC. Good turnout, everyone's pretending to care about local elections again.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The BJP is back, baby! After a ten-year break, they've bulldozed their way back into control of the NMMC. Looks like विकास (progress) is back on the menu, folks.</p>
<p>They grabbed 66 seats in the Navi Mumbai Municipal Corporation. Word on the street is that voters actually showed up this time, which is a shocker. Usually, these c...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-18</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-18/bjp-nmmc-win.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Teen Killed: Love, Lies, and Nerul Nightmare</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-18/nerul-murder-teen.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: An 18-year-old is dead after a fight over a girl in Nerul. The twist? Her little brother is allegedly involved. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Sector 21 love triangle took a deadly turn this week. Cops say Nikhil Jadhav, 18, was beaten to death near the old Nerul dumping ground. What started as a teenage squabble ended with a boy gone and five others in custody, including the girl’s younger brother. Seriously, what is going on with these kids?</p>
<p>According t...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-18</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-18/nerul-murder-teen.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NMMC Election Results: Shock Landslide, Incumbent Party Swept Out</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-18/nmmc-election-tsunami.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The opposition just steamrolled the NMMC elections. Expect dramatic changes at the civic HQ in Belapur. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Belapur's political landscape just got nuked. Early results show a near-total wipeout for the ruling coalition. Sector 15 is buzzing – nobody saw this coming.</p>
<p>Multiple sources are calling it a "referendum on corruption." Remember the ₹80 Crore road resurfacing scam? Voters sure did.</p>
<p>The opposition, riding a wave of anti...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-18</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-18/nmmc-election-tsunami.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Elderly Navi Mumbaikar Loses ₹4 Crore to Scammers</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-17/cyber-fraud-crore.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A senior citizen in Navi Mumbai got scammed out of ₹4 Crore. Scammers are working overtime, and maybe it's time to hide under a rock.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another day, another cybercrime. This time, some poor soul in Navi Mumbai kissed ₹4 Crore goodbye thanks to those digital bandits. Seriously, is anyone safe?</p>
<p>Details are scarce, but the Times of India reports that an elderly resident fell victim to sophisticated cyber fraud. Crores, GONE. This isn'...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-17</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-17/cyber-fraud-crore.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tamhini Ghat Murder: Key Suspect Nabbed by Police</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-17/tamhini-ghat-arrest.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Police caught the main guy in the Tamhini Ghat murder case. About damn time they did. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Navi Mumbai police finally caught a break in the Tamhini Ghat murder case, nabbing a key suspect. After weeks of what felt like a dead end, investigators got their guy. </p>
<p>The accused was picked up near Panvel early this morning. Details are still trickling in, but sources within the Kharghar police station confirm it's a major development. T...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-17</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-17/tamhini-ghat-arrest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Airport signal woes? Telcos want TRAI to fix.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-17/airport-signal-trouble.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Mobile networks near the new Navi Mumbai airport are reportedly a mess. Telcos are begging TRAI to step in before it becomes a total communication black hole.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Chaos is brewing before the first flight even takes off. Telcos are officially fed up with signal issues plaguing the area around the upcoming Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA).</p>
<p>Apparently, getting a decent mobile signal near Sector 112 is harder than finding parking...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-17</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-17/airport-signal-trouble.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Chougule Family Owns Airoli-Digha: Dynasty Confirmed</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/chougule-airoli-digha.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The Chougule family basically runs Airoli-Digha now, politically speaking. Is anyone <em>really</em> surprised that local politics feels like a family business?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Looks like the Chougules are the new kings of Airoli-Digha. Newsband is reporting that the family has solidified its political grip on the area.</p>
<p>Basically, if you want anything done in Wards 1 through whatever, you're going through them. Ward dominance confirmed.</p>
<p>I...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-16</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/chougule-airoli-digha.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BJP Claims Mumbai Mayor: 100% Guarantee? Doubtful.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/bjp-mayor-claim.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: BJP leader claims they'll snag the Mumbai mayoral seat after the 2026 BMC elections. Bold words, considering Mumbai's voters might have other ideas. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>So, some BJP leader is strutting around saying they've got the Mumbai mayoral election in the bag for 2026. Like, 100% guaranteed. Did they ask Mumbai? </p>
<p>According to <em>The Economic Times</em>, this claim comes straight from the Maharashtra Assembly. No specific names are mentioned...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-16</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/bjp-mayor-claim.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ward 10D: Votes Counted, Chaos Ensues?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/ward-10d-election.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Counting started at 10 am for NMMC Ward 10D. Prepare for political theatrics, maybe some chai spills.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Buckle up, Nerul. The ballot counting bonanza for NMMC Ward 10D kicked off at 10 this morning, according to <em>some</em> news outlets. We're picturing more drama than a Balaji Telefilms production.</p>
<p>Expect the usual suspects: frantic phone calls, whispered deals, and nervous candidates mainlining caffeine. The real question is: w...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-16</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/ward-10d-election.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Voters Show Up; Thane Yawned</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/voter-turnout-navi-mumbai.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Navi Mumbai crushed Thane in voter turnout for civic polls. Apparently, someone actually cares about Panvel's potholes.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Navi Mumbai showed up to vote like they were promised free pav bhaji, clocking a sweet 57% turnout in the Maharashtra civic body elections. Thane, meanwhile, barely managed 54%. Were they all stuck in Ghodbunder Road traffic? Probably.</p>
<p>The numbers put Navi Mumbai at the top of the MMR region. Panvel, especially,...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-16</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/voter-turnout-navi-mumbai.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Nerul: Multiple Cylinder Blasts Rock Sector 20</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/nerul-blast.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Multiple cylinders exploded in Nerul Sector 20, causing panic. We're guessing someone's chai plans are ruined.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Sector 20 just got a whole lot louder. Residents reported hearing a series of explosions around [TIME - confirm time of incident]. Initial reports suggest 4-5 cylinders detonated.</p>
<p>The cause is still unknown, but we're betting someone wasn't paying attention while changing their gas connection. No official statement yet f...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-16</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/nerul-blast.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>