<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>BMC Polls: Mahayuti Promises Mumbai Makeover (Again)</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bcm-mahauati-manifesto.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Mahayuti's BMC manifesto is here, promising everything from Marathi housing to global city status. Are we holding our breath? Not really.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Mahayuti alliance is at it again, dangling shiny promises before the upcoming BMC elections. This time, they're waving the flag of "Marathi pride" while promising a Mumbai transformed by 2030. Did anyone ask for another transformation?</p>
<p>The manifesto, unveiled earlier today, pledges housing ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bcm-mahauati-manifesto.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Land Dispute Turns Violent: HC Clerk Assaulted</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-land-attack.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: An HC clerk was attacked during a land possession in Kharghar. This is what happens when Navi Mumbai property disputes get <em>real</em> personal.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Chaos erupted in Kharghar's Sector 35 when a land possession process turned ugly. A High Court clerk, tasked with overseeing the transfer, found himself on the receiving end of a father-son beatdown, according to the First Information Report.</p>
<p>The incident occurred during the execution ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-land-attack.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai: Father-Son Duo Attack Court Clerk</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/court-clerk-attack.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A High Court clerk was assaulted and threatened in Navi Mumbai during a land possession. Sounds like someone didn't want to give up their plot of land.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Trouble flared during a land possession process in Navi Mumbai. A High Court clerk was allegedly assaulted and threatened by a father-son duo. This happened while the clerk was carrying out their official duties.</p>
<p>The incident occurred in connection with a land dispute case. Report...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/court-clerk-attack.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Exam Talk: Registrations Jump, Records Broken (Again)</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/pariksha-record.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: "Pariksha Pe Charcha" registrations blew past last year's record. Modi fever (or exam stress) is clearly still a thing.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another year, another registration record shattered for "Pariksha Pe Charcha" (PPC) – clocking in at a bonkers 4.3 crore! Last year's 3.53 crore, which earned a Guinness World Record, now looks like chillar change.</p>
<p>Apparently, everyone wants a piece of Modi's exam advice. Registrations closed January 29th. Stude...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/pariksha-record.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Thieves Busted: Stolen Loot Recovered in Vashi</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-theft-arrests.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Three thieves are in NMMC lockup after a Vashi bust. Police recovered stolen jewellery and appliances – a bad day for crime, a good day for justice (finally!).</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Vashi police station just notched a win. Three individuals are cooling their heels after getting pinched for a string of thefts across the node. Forget cat burglars, these guys were hitting houses and making off with anything they could carry.</p>
<p>Acting on a tip-off, the ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-theft-arrests.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>RCB? MI? WPL Clash Returns To DY Patil!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-mi-rcb.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Mumbai Indians Women face Royal Challengers Bangalore Women at DY Patil Stadium. Get ready for screaming fans and overpriced vada pav.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Think the men's IPL is intense? Get ready for the Women's Premier League! The Mumbai Indians Women are set to battle Royal Challengers Bangalore Women at the DY Patil Stadium. First match is gonna be a banger. Forget your Sunday snooze; this is way more exciting.</p>
<p>Historically, MI Women have domina...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-mi-rcb.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Shinde Tells Navi Mumbai: End Political 'Monopoly'</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/shinde-monopoly-navi-mumbai.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Eknath Shinde wants voters to dump current leaders. Translation: The Shiv Sena's ready to rumble in Navi Mumbai.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Eknath Shinde, Maharashtra's Deputy CM, swung into Navi Mumbai yesterday with a not-so-subtle message: shake up the political landscape. Addressing a rally in Vashi, Shinde called on voters to break the "monopoly of entrenched leadership". In simpler terms, he's saying "out with the old, in with the…well, you get it."</p>
<p>...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/shinde-monopoly-navi-mumbai.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Bollywood Blows Up DY Patil For WPL Opener</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-opening-bollywood.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The WPL 2026 opening ceremony at DY Patil was a Bollywood extravaganza. Harnaaz Sandhu, Jacqueline Fernandez, and Honey Singh all performed, because of course they did.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The DY Patil Stadium got a Bollywood-sized shot of adrenaline last night, kicking off the 2026 Women's Premier League. Harnaaz Sandhu graced the stage, because apparently being Miss Universe wasn't enough excitement for one lifetime. Jacqueline Fernandez brought the danc...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-opening-bollywood.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>₹16 Lakh Seized in Vashi Car Stop</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-cash-seized.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A flying squad snagged ₹16.16 lakh in unmarked cash from a Vashi car during an election patrol. Someone's having a bad day and might need a new accountant.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Election Commission's MCC team pulled over a vehicle near Vashi Plaza yesterday. Inside, they found a cool ₹16.16 lakh in undeclared cash. No receipts, no explanations. Just stacks of paper.</p>
<p>The flying squad, bless their suspicious hearts, impounded the moolah immediately....</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-cash-seized.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Naik to Shinde: Don't Underestimate Me</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/naik-shinde-feud.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Ganesh Naik, NCP heavyweight, just told Deputy CM Shinde not to mess with him regarding the upcoming NMMC elections. Basically, election season in Navi Mumbai is officially spicy.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>NCP strongman Ganesh Naik has thrown down the gauntlet to Deputy Chief Minister Devendra Fadnavis, warning him not to underestimate his influence in the upcoming Navi Mumbai Municipal Corporation (NMMC) elections. The declaration came at a party meeting in Bel...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/naik-shinde-feud.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>WPL 2026: Navi Mumbai's Cricket Fever Returns!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-2026-navi.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The Women's Premier League 2026 is coming, with games in Navi Mumbai. Get ready for some sixes (and maybe some traffic). </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Navi Mumbai is gearing up for more cricket action. The WPL 2026 schedule dropped, and DY Patil Stadium is hosting a chunk of the matches. Forget the IPL; this is where the real drama happens (probably).</p>
<p>All five teams are back, with a few captain changes. Word on the street (aka, WION) is that the squads are l...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-2026-navi.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Wipro Bets Big: 145,000 Sq Ft Navi Mumbai Office</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wipro-navi-mumbai.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Wipro just leased a massive office space in Navi Mumbai, signaling continued investment. Guess those TCS guys in Airoli have some new competition.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Wipro just dropped a cool 145,000 sq ft on a new Navi Mumbai office. Forget the Bandra-Kurla Complex; the real action is shifting east, folks. This isn't just some tiny satellite office; it's a full-blown commitment to the satellite city.</p>
<p>Details are still emerging, but we know the spa...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wipro-navi-mumbai.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Dust Devils Down: 19 Sites Shut, 173 Fined</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/dust-sites-shut.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: NMMC cracked down on 19 construction sites for spewing dust. Developers are coughing up fines—hopefully, that’ll help them clean up their act.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another day, another dust storm choking Navi Mumbai. This time, though, the NMMC actually did something. They swooped in and shut down 19 construction sites for violating pollution norms. About time.</p>
<p>According to Mid-day, a whopping 173 developers also got slapped with penalty notices. Whi...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/dust-sites-shut.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DY Patil: Expect runs in MI vs DC clash</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/dy-patil-pitch.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: WPL returns to DY Patil Stadium. Expect a batter-friendly pitch, but pace bowlers might enjoy some bounce.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another day, another chance to witness some sixes. The Women's Premier League returns to the DY Patil Stadium. Forget slow, turning tracks. Word on the street (and from Business Standard) is that this pitch is ready for some serious hitting.</p>
<p>Batters, sharpen those blades! The pitch at DY Patil typically offers a good bounce ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/dy-patil-pitch.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Giants Stomp Warriorz: WPL 2026 Kicks Off!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/giants-warriorz-wpl.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Gujarat Giants won their first WPL match against UP Warriorz by 10 runs in a thriller. The vibe at the DY Patil was electric, even if the actual cricket was occasionally… chaotic.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Women's Premier League 2026 exploded into action at the DY Patil Stadium last night. The Gujarat Giants clawed their way to a 10-run victory over the UP Warriorz, and the crowd went wild.</p>
<p>Chasing 163, the Warriorz stumbled. Sector 5 residents probab...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/giants-warriorz-wpl.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>WPL Lockdowns: DY Patil Zone Sealed Till Jan 17</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-road-closures.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Roads near DY Patil Stadium are closed until January 17 for the Women's Premier League. Hope you like detours, because you're about to become an expert.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Heads up, folks! If your daily commute involves navigating the concrete jungle around DY Patil Stadium in Nerul, prepare for some detours. Thanks to the WPL 2026 shenanigans, certain roads are now off-limits until January 17.</p>
<p>According to Mumbai Live, the closures are in full eff...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-road-closures.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BJP Candidate Added to NMMC Ward List After Court Order</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bjp-nmmc-court.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Bombay High Court says NMMC must include BJP candidate in the upcoming civic polls. So much for streamlining the ballot, eh?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Looks like someone's name got lost in the NMMC shuffle. The Bombay High Court just ordered the Navi Mumbai Municipal Corporation to include a BJP candidate on the ballot for the upcoming civic elections.</p>
<p>Apparently, there was some kind of omission in Ward Number 114 (Sector 14, Vashi). The BJP nominee's pap...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bjp-nmmc-court.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ward 17A Election Delayed: More Chaos in NMMC?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/ward-17a-delay.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The Ward 17A election is on hold, thanks to some legal shenanigans. Honestly, does anything in the NMMC <em>not</em> get delayed?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another election delay? You bet. This time, it's Ward 17A feeling the heat, according to Lokshahi English News. Some kind of stay has been issued, freezing the electoral process faster than you can say "political maneuvering."</p>
<p>What's Ward 17A anyway? Think of it as that awkward zone near Nerul, always ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/ward-17a-delay.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sharma & Vasistha Debut: MI vs. DC is On!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-debuts-dc.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Delhi Capitals are bowling against Mumbai Indians with Nandani Sharma and Triveni Vasistha making their debut; finally, some fresh blood on the pitch!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Women's Premier League saw some shake-ups today as the Delhi Capitals chose to bowl first against the Mumbai Indians. It's about time someone mixed things up; frankly, some of us were starting to doze off.</p>
<p>But the real buzz? Nandani Sharma and Triveni Vasistha are making their ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-debuts-dc.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Capitals Bowl First: MI Batting in IPL Clash</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/capitals-bowl-first.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Delhi Capitals won the toss and chose to bowl against Mumbai Indians. Good news for Capitals fans, maybe bad news for pizza delivery guys expecting late-night orders from MI supporters.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The coin landed in Delhi's favor. They're sending Mumbai in to bat first at the Wankhede. Rishabh Pant seems confident. Rohit Sharma probably isn't thrilled.</p>
<p>Why bowl first? Pant cited "dew factor" and a desire to chase. Translation: Mumbai's bowl...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/capitals-bowl-first.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>