<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>Kharghar, Ulwe, Dronagiri face water cuts starting Sunday</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-water-cut.html</link>
            <description><p>Residents in Kharghar, Ulwe, and Dronagiri nodes brace for water supply disruptions starting this Sunday. The City and Industrial Development Corporation (CIDCO) announced planned maintenance impacting the Hetawane dam pipeline.</p>
<p>The shutdown begins at 10:00 AM on Sunday, July 7th, and stretches until 10:00 AM on Monday, July 8th. Water supply will be completely suspended during this period, CIDCO officials confirmed. Residents are advised to store sufficient water in advance. </p>
<p>T...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-water-cut.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Hindu Group Protests "Anti-Religious" Ad at Vashi Showroom</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-ad-protest.html</link>
            <description><p>A demonstration erupted outside a clothing store in Vashi Sector 17 yesterday afternoon. Members of a local Hindu organization alleged that the store's advertisement was offensive to their religious sentiments. The protest caused a brief disruption to traffic near the station. </p>
<p>Demonstrators gathered around 3 PM, chanting slogans and demanding the removal of the advertisement. Police arrived on the scene and managed to contain the protest. No arrests were made. </p>
<p>The contentious ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-ad-protest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Cop Vanishes; Corruption Letter Surfaces</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cop-gone-missing.html</link>
            <description><p>A police constable from Navi Mumbai has gone missing, sparking a probe into alleged corruption within the force. A letter, purportedly written by the missing officer, implicates a senior inspector in illicit activities. The constable's wife has filed a formal complaint, prompting an immediate inquiry. </p>
<p>The missing constable, identified as Sachin Mane, was last seen near the Belapur CBD station. The letter, now in the hands of investigators, details alleged extortion rackets and protect...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cop-gone-missing.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cyber Grift: Student Duped Out of ₹2 Lakh</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cyber-fraud-nerul.html</link>
            <description><p>A Nerul student lost ₹2 lakh, including scholarship funds, to a sophisticated cyber fraud this week. The incident underscores the rising threat of online scams targeting Navi Mumbai residents.</p>
<p>The victim, a student residing in Sector 21, received a fraudulent link disguised as a scholarship disbursement notification. Upon clicking, the link redirected to a fake banking interface that mimicked the IDBI bank's portal. The student entered their credentials, unknowingly compromising their ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cyber-fraud-nerul.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Teen's Fake Instagram: Koparkhairane Man Arrested</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/fake-insta-arrest.html</link>
            <description><p>Navi Mumbai police apprehended a 22-year-old Koparkhairane resident for creating a bogus Instagram profile impersonating a local teenager. The accused, identified as [Accused's Name - if available], allegedly posted sexually explicit content and images to harass the victim. The cybercrime unit of the Navi Mumbai police acted on a complaint filed by the teen's parents. </p>
<p>The investigation revealed the accused had been stalking the victim online for several months. He obtained personal de...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/fake-insta-arrest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NMMC Turns Commute into Chapter Time</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/NMMC-reads-books.html</link>
            <description><p>Navi Mumbai's commuters can now bury themselves in a book instead of their phones. The NMMC launched a unique initiative this week: free mini-libraries at key bus stops. The goal? To turn transit time into reading time.</p>
<p>The pilot project kicked off at the Vashi Sector 17 bus depot. Commuters can borrow books without any formal membership. The collection includes a mix of genres, from thrillers to biographies. The NMMC plans to expand the program to other nodes based on its initial succ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/NMMC-reads-books.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>