<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>Nerul Student Duped: ₹2 Lakh Scholarship Vanishes in Cyber Scam</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cyber-scam-nerul.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Nerul student got fleeced for ₹2 lakhs in scholarship money. Cyber crooks are getting bolder, and Navi Mumbai is the new hunting ground.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another day, another cyber scam. This time, a student from Nerul's Sector 21 lost ₹2 lakhs—including hard-earned scholarship funds—to online fraudsters. The con artists, posing as bank officials, sweet-talked the student into handing over sensitive account details under the guise of a 'verification p...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cyber-scam-nerul.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kharghar, Ulwe, Dronagiri: No Water Sunday. Tankers Incoming?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/no-water-sunday.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Dry taps hit Kharghar, Ulwe, and Dronagiri this Sunday. CIDCO's fixing something, so fill those buckets and prepare for a classic Navi Mumbai water crisis.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Heads up, folks in Kharghar, Ulwe, and Dronagiri: Sunday's looking parched. CIDCO announced a water supply disruption for “urgent repairs.” Translation: something broke. The official line is that supply will be off from 10 AM to 6 PM. Unofficially? Pack extra patience. </p>
<p>The di...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/no-water-sunday.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COVID Outbreak at Navi Mumbai School: 18 Test Positive</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/covid-school-nerul.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: 18 students at a Nerul school test positive for COVID. Back to masks and hand sanitizer, folks; the pandemic's encore is here.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The scene at Ryan International School, Nerul, is a bit of a mess today after a cluster of COVID cases emerged, sending parents into a frenzy. Eighteen students have tested positive, prompting the school to implement immediate safety measures. Sector 45 aunties are not happy.</p>
<p>While NMMC health officials a...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/covid-school-nerul.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Pro-Hindu Group Stages Protest Over Ad Outside Vashi Clothing Store</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/protest-vashi-ad.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Ad sparks outrage in Vashi. Pro-Hindu group claims it's offensive and stages a protest outside the store. Prepare for traffic snarls.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Expect some chaos in Sector 17 this afternoon. A pro-Hindu group is staging a protest outside a clothing brand showroom. They say the ad is offensive to their religious sentiments. The vibe outside is tense, with slogans and chants echoing through the area. </p>
<p>The specific objection? The group isn't ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/protest-vashi-ad.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Read on the Run: NMMC Turns NMMT Buses into Mobile Libraries</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bus-books-nmmc.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Ditch doomscrolling; grab a book on your commute. NMMC turns NMMT buses into rolling libraries, offering Sector 17 aunties and Cyber City execs some literary respite. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Forget fighting for a seat; now you can battle for the last copy of Chetan Bhagat on the 520 route. The NMMC, in a move that's either genius or a logistical nightmare, has kitted out select NMMT buses with mini-libraries. Passengers can now borrow books for free while nav...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bus-books-nmmc.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Nerul creep: Man held for obscene teen Insta fake</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/insta-creep-arrest.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Nerul teen harassed with fake Instagram profile. Cyber cops nabbed the culprit; turns out, it's an uncle from Sector 21. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>If you thought Instagram was just for brunch pics and influencer scams, think again. A 19-year-old from Nerul found out the hard way when some loser created a fake account in her name and started posting obscene garbage. Think morphed photos and creepy DMs sent to her contacts. Nightmare fuel.</p>
<p>The Cyber Crime ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/insta-creep-arrest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Airport Naming Protest: Activists to Decide Next Steps Today</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-naming-protest.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The Navi Mumbai airport naming saga continues. Protest leaders meet today to decide if more chaos is on the horizon.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The fight over who gets their name plastered on the Navi Mumbai International Airport isn't over. Leaders of the protests demanding the airport be named after D.B. Patil are meeting today in Panvel to decide their next move. Will they double down on the gridlock, or find a new pressure point?</p>
<p>The last round of prot...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-naming-protest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Metro Line 1 Ready to Vibe: Oscillation Trials Complete</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-line-1-trials.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Navi Mumbai Metro Line 1 passes oscillation trials. Get ready to ditch the auto rickshaw; trains are coming soon. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Sector 1’s elevated steel is about to get a whole lot busier. The Navi Mumbai Metro Line 1, linking Belapur to Pendhar, just wrapped up its oscillation trials. This means the Commissioner of Railway Safety (CRS) is about to give the green light. No more sweating it out on the Thane-Belapur road. </p>
<p>CIDCO is saying oper...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-line-1-trials.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Metro Line 1: Pendhar to Central Park Trial Run a Success</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trial-success.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Metro Line 1 zips from Pendhar to Central Park. CIDCO’s party trick worked; now just waiting for the official green light.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Sector buzz is building because the Navi Mumbai Metro Line 1 just aced its trial run between Pendhar and Central Park. Yesterday, the train successfully navigated the 11-km stretch, proving that someone in CIDCO knows what they're doing. The route includes stations at Pendhar, Belapur Farm, Sector 34, Panchanand, an...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trial-success.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Missing Navi Mumbai Cop Claims Corruption: Sector 17 Drama</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-corruption.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Navi Mumbai police officer vanishes, leaving behind a letter alleging corruption. Wife reports him missing, adding fuel to the fire in Sector 17.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The NMMC police force is dealing with a full-blown crisis this week. An officer from Sector 17 has gone AWOL, but not before allegedly penning a letter accusing a senior officer of shady dealings. According to the wife, she filed a missing person report when he didn't return home from duty. In...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-corruption.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>