<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Metro Line 1 Completes Oscillation Trials</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trials-done.html</link>
            <description><p>Navi Mumbai Metro Line 1 cleared a critical hurdle this week, concluding its oscillation trials along the entire 11.1 km stretch from Belapur to Pendhar. The trials, overseen by the Research Designs and Standards Organisation (RDSO), are a prerequisite for commercial operations. While the RDSO certification is pending, CIDCO anticipates a green light within weeks, potentially paving the way for a late-2024 launch. </p>
<p>The oscillation trials, a series of rigorous tests evaluating the metro...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trials-done.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kharghar, Ulwe Residents Face 24-Hour Water Cut: Pipeline Repairs Underway</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-water-cut.html</link>
            <description><p>Residents of Kharghar, Ulwe, and Dronagiri will experience a 24-hour water supply disruption starting this Sunday, NMMC officials have announced. The shutdown, commencing at 10:00 AM on Sunday, June 9th, is due to urgent repairs on a major pipeline near the Hetawane Dam. Specifically, a faulty valve requires replacement to prevent further leakage and ensure consistent pressure across the region.</p>
<p>The disruption impacts Sectors 1 to 30 in Kharghar, encompassing key residential areas like...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-water-cut.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Pendhar to Central Park Metro Line Completes Successful Trial Run</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trial-run.html</link>
            <description><p>CIDCO completed the trial run of the Navi Mumbai Metro Line 1, Phase 1, from Pendhar to Central Park this week, signaling a potential near-term opening for the much-anticipated route. The initial run focused on evaluating signalling synchronization and track integrity across the 5.14 km stretch. While an official launch date remains unconfirmed, sources within CIDCO suggest operations could commence before the monsoon. </p>
<p>The Pendhar-Central Park section is the first phase of the broader...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trial-run.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>All-Party Meeting to Decide Fate of Airport Naming Protests</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-naming-protests.html</link>
            <description><p>A crucial all-party meeting is scheduled today to determine the future course of action regarding protests over the naming of the Navi Mumbai International Airport. The contentious issue, pitting supporters of D.B. Patil against those advocating for a different nomenclature, has simmered for years, occasionally boiling over into disruptive demonstrations. Today's gathering, convened by local political leaders, aims to forge a consensus and potentially de-escalate tensions that have threatened...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-naming-protests.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Bajrang Dal Protests Clothing Ad Outside Vashi Showroom</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bajrang-dal-protest.html</link>
            <description><p>Members of the Bajrang Dal staged a protest outside a clothing showroom in Vashi Sector 17 yesterday, objecting to the imagery in the brand's latest advertising campaign. The group, numbering approximately 50 individuals, gathered outside the Soch showroom at the Inorbit Mall vicinity around 4 PM, chanting slogans and demanding the removal of what they deemed "offensive" content. </p>
<p>The advertisement in question, prominently displayed above the store entrance, features a woman in traditi...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bajrang-dal-protest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kharghar Man Held: Teen's Fake Instagram Account Case Solved</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/instagram-fake-account.html</link>
            <description><p>A 23-year-old Kharghar resident was apprehended this week for creating a fake Instagram account impersonating a local teenager and posting obscene content. The cybercrime unit of the Navi Mumbai police, acting on a complaint filed by the victim's family from Sector 12, traced the IP address to a residence near Little World Mall. </p>
<p>The accused, identified as Rohan Sharma, allegedly created the profile using a stolen photograph and proceeded to upload sexually suggestive material, causing...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/instagram-fake-account.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kharghar Student Duped Out of Scholarship Funds in Cyber Fraud</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cyber-fraud-kharghar.html</link>
            <description><p>A student residing in Sector 12, Kharghar, lost ₹2 lakh to cyber fraud, a sum that included crucial scholarship money. The incident, reported to the Cyber Crime cell of the Navi Mumbai Police, underscores the escalating threat of online scams targeting vulnerable individuals, especially students dependent on financial aid.</p>
<p>The student, whose name is being withheld, received a fraudulent link disguised as an update from their bank. Upon clicking the link and entering their credentials, ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cyber-fraud-kharghar.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Covid Returns: 18 Students Test Positive in Nerul School</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nerul-school-covid.html</link>
            <description><p>Eighteen students at a private school in Sector 21, Nerul, tested positive for Covid-19 this week, prompting a temporary closure of the campus. The incident, confirmed by NMMC health officials, marks a localized resurgence of the virus following months of relative calm across the satellite city.</p>
<p>The initial case was detected in a Class VIII student during routine screening on Monday. Subsequent testing revealed a cluster of infections concentrated primarily within two classrooms. While...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nerul-school-covid.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NMMC Transforms Bus Shelters into Literary Havens for Commuters</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/NMMC-bus-libraries.html</link>
            <description><p>Commuters awaiting buses in Navi Mumbai can now indulge in a spot of reading, courtesy of a novel initiative by the Navi Mumbai Municipal Corporation (NMMC). Select bus shelters across the city have been transformed into miniature libraries, stocked with a diverse collection of books ranging from fiction to non-fiction. </p>
<p>The initiative, spearheaded by the NMMC's library department, aims to promote reading habits among citizens and make waiting time more productive. The first such 'bus ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/NMMC-bus-libraries.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Missing Navi Mumbai Cop's Letter Alleges Senior Officer Corruption</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-corruption.html</link>
            <description><p>A cloud of suspicion hangs over the Navi Mumbai police force after Police Constable Sandeep Jadhav of the NRI Coastal police station went missing, leaving behind a letter accusing a senior officer of corruption. Jadhav's wife filed a missing person complaint at the same station, setting off an internal investigation that threatens to expose rot within the ranks.</p>
<p>The handwritten letter, now in the possession of the Raigad police, details alleged extortion and abuse of power by the unnam...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-corruption.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>