<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>Chougule Family Owns Airoli-Digha: Dynasty Confirmed</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/chougule-airoli-digha.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The Chougule family basically runs Airoli-Digha now, politically speaking. Is anyone <em>really</em> surprised that local politics feels like a family business?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Looks like the Chougules are the new kings of Airoli-Digha. Newsband is reporting that the family has solidified its political grip on the area.</p>
<p>Basically, if you want anything done in Wards 1 through whatever, you're going through them. Ward dominance confirmed.</p>
<p>I...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-16</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/chougule-airoli-digha.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BJP Claims Mumbai Mayor: 100% Guarantee? Doubtful.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/bjp-mayor-claim.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: BJP leader claims they'll snag the Mumbai mayoral seat after the 2026 BMC elections. Bold words, considering Mumbai's voters might have other ideas. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>So, some BJP leader is strutting around saying they've got the Mumbai mayoral election in the bag for 2026. Like, 100% guaranteed. Did they ask Mumbai? </p>
<p>According to <em>The Economic Times</em>, this claim comes straight from the Maharashtra Assembly. No specific names are mentioned...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-16</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/bjp-mayor-claim.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ward 10D: Votes Counted, Chaos Ensues?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/ward-10d-election.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Counting started at 10 am for NMMC Ward 10D. Prepare for political theatrics, maybe some chai spills.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Buckle up, Nerul. The ballot counting bonanza for NMMC Ward 10D kicked off at 10 this morning, according to <em>some</em> news outlets. We're picturing more drama than a Balaji Telefilms production.</p>
<p>Expect the usual suspects: frantic phone calls, whispered deals, and nervous candidates mainlining caffeine. The real question is: w...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-16</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/ward-10d-election.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Voters Show Up; Thane Yawned</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/voter-turnout-navi-mumbai.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Navi Mumbai crushed Thane in voter turnout for civic polls. Apparently, someone actually cares about Panvel's potholes.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Navi Mumbai showed up to vote like they were promised free pav bhaji, clocking a sweet 57% turnout in the Maharashtra civic body elections. Thane, meanwhile, barely managed 54%. Were they all stuck in Ghodbunder Road traffic? Probably.</p>
<p>The numbers put Navi Mumbai at the top of the MMR region. Panvel, especially,...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-16</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/voter-turnout-navi-mumbai.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Nerul: Multiple Cylinder Blasts Rock Sector 20</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/nerul-blast.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Multiple cylinders exploded in Nerul Sector 20, causing panic. We're guessing someone's chai plans are ruined.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Sector 20 just got a whole lot louder. Residents reported hearing a series of explosions around [TIME - confirm time of incident]. Initial reports suggest 4-5 cylinders detonated.</p>
<p>The cause is still unknown, but we're betting someone wasn't paying attention while changing their gas connection. No official statement yet f...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-16</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-16/nerul-blast.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kharghar Landlords Busted for Illegal Tenants</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-tenant-bust.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Cops raided Kharghar apartments, snagging illegal foreign nationals. Landlords are in deep trouble, facing charges for renting to them.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Kharghar landlords are about to learn a very expensive lesson: check your tenant's paperwork. Last night's NMMC raid, spearheaded by the Kharghar police, netted several foreign nationals residing illegally in the area.</p>
<p>The swoop, focused on Sector 35 and Sector 12, resulted in multiple detentions...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-tenant-bust.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1100 Students: Human Chain for Votes?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/human-chain-votes.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Over a thousand students linked up to promote voting in the 2026 NMMC elections. Is a human chain enough to break through the apathy? </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Forget the usual rallies. This time, 1100 students from various Navi Mumbai schools and colleges formed a human chain yesterday morning. The goal? To raise awareness about the upcoming Navi Mumbai Municipal Corporation (NMMC) elections in 2026. </p>
<p>The chain snaked through Sector 15 in Vashi, near th...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/human-chain-votes.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Poll Code? Mayor's Promise Sparks Fury.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/mayor-poll-code.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Maharashtra SEC investigates mayor for promising development based on religion. Political storms are brewing, and election officers are ready for the fallout.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Did Navi Mumbai just enter a time machine? A newly elected mayor seems to think promising ward development based on religion is A-OK. Maharashtra State Election Commissioner Dinesh Waghmare isn't amused.</p>
<p>The mayor's statement, made at a recent public gathering in Panvel, sp...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/mayor-poll-code.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BJP, Congress Brawl Over 'Ladki Bahin' Scheme</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/ladki-bahin-fight.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: BJP says Congress is against the Ladki Bahin Yojana. Because apparently helping girls is now a political stance? </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Chandrashekhar Bawankule, Maharashtra Revenue Minister, is not happy. He's accusing Congress of opposing the Ladki Bahin Yojana, a welfare scheme launched in 2024. According to Bawankule, talking about helping girls isn't against election rules. The municipal corporation elections are January 15th, so naturally, everyone's y...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/ladki-bahin-fight.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Transgender Voters: "Use Your Voice, Navi Mumbai!"</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/transgender-vote-nmmc.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The transgender community is pushing for voter turnout in the upcoming NMMC elections. Maybe this time, politicians will actually listen to what they have to say.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>With Navi Mumbai's election season heating up (some might say melting, given the current humidity), the transgender community is making a big push: Vote! The goal? To get more people to the polls and, hopefully, get some actual representation in the NMMC.</p>
<p>Community lead...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/transgender-vote-nmmc.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>MI steamrolls DC: WPL trophy stays in Mumbai</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/mi-wins-wpl.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Mumbai Indians crushed Delhi Capitals by 50 runs in the WPL final. Another trophy for MI – guess Ambani's still smiling.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Mumbai Indians defended their WPL crown in style, thrashing the Delhi Capitals by 50 runs at the DY Patil Stadium last night. DC, chasing 165, crumbled under pressure, managing a paltry 113 all out.</p>
<p>MI's batting lineup fired, with Harmanpreet Kaur leading the charge with a quickfire 45. Sector 15, CBD Belap...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/mi-wins-wpl.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BJP, Shiv Sena Face Off in Navi Mumbai Civic Polls</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bjp-shiv-sena-nm.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: BJP and Shiv Sena are clashing hard in Navi Mumbai's civic elections. Expect fireworks and maybe some unexpected alliances – or at least some spicy memes.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The battle for Navi Mumbai's civic pie is heating up, and it’s BJP vs. Shiv Sena… again. Forget cozy alliances; this is a full-blown turf war for control of the NMMC. Sector who? This isn't about sectors, it's about supremacy.</p>
<p>What's fueling the fire? Think ego, think power, an...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bjp-shiv-sena-nm.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Transgender Navi Mumbaikars: Vote for change!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/transgender-vote-push.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The transgender community is pushing for higher voter turnout in the upcoming NMMC elections. Will anyone listen, or will Sector 17 keep pretending they don't exist?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Navi Mumbai's transgender community is making a push to get more people to the polls for the upcoming NMMC election. They are urging <em>everyone</em> to vote, hoping to make their voices heard.</p>
<p>"Every vote counts," said a representative from the community at a rally...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/transgender-vote-push.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Mahayuti's Election Promise: Half-Price Bus for Women</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/mahayuti-bus-pass.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Mahayuti's manifesto for Mumbai's civic polls includes a 50% bus fare cut for women. Think of all the extra vada pav one could buy with that. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Mahayuti alliance (BJP, Shiv Sena, NCP) just dropped their manifesto for the upcoming Mumbai civic elections. The big promise? Women get half-price bus tickets. </p>
<p>Imagine ₹10 trips from Panvel to Belapur costing just ₹5. According to the manifesto, this aims to ease travel for women and...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/mahayuti-bus-pass.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>WPL 2026: MI Still On Top, But For How Long?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-2026-standings.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: MI leads the WPL 2026 standings as of Jan 11th. Can they keep the crown, or will RCB finally make a push?.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Women's Premier League 2026 season is heating up, and as of January 11th, the Mumbai Indians are still clinging to the top spot. But don't get too comfortable, folks. </p>
<p>RCB is breathing down their necks, followed by DC, UPW, and GGT. The standings are tighter than the traffic on the Sion-Panvel highway during peak hours.<...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-2026-standings.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BMC Polls: Mahayuti Promises Mumbai Makeover (Again)</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bcm-mahauati-manifesto.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Mahayuti's BMC manifesto is here, promising everything from Marathi housing to global city status. Are we holding our breath? Not really.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Mahayuti alliance is at it again, dangling shiny promises before the upcoming BMC elections. This time, they're waving the flag of "Marathi pride" while promising a Mumbai transformed by 2030. Did anyone ask for another transformation?</p>
<p>The manifesto, unveiled earlier today, pledges housing ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bcm-mahauati-manifesto.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Land Dispute Turns Violent: HC Clerk Assaulted</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-land-attack.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: An HC clerk was attacked during a land possession in Kharghar. This is what happens when Navi Mumbai property disputes get <em>real</em> personal.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Chaos erupted in Kharghar's Sector 35 when a land possession process turned ugly. A High Court clerk, tasked with overseeing the transfer, found himself on the receiving end of a father-son beatdown, according to the First Information Report.</p>
<p>The incident occurred during the execution ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-land-attack.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai: Father-Son Duo Attack Court Clerk</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/court-clerk-attack.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A High Court clerk was assaulted and threatened in Navi Mumbai during a land possession. Sounds like someone didn't want to give up their plot of land.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Trouble flared during a land possession process in Navi Mumbai. A High Court clerk was allegedly assaulted and threatened by a father-son duo. This happened while the clerk was carrying out their official duties.</p>
<p>The incident occurred in connection with a land dispute case. Report...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/court-clerk-attack.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Exam Talk: Registrations Jump, Records Broken (Again)</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/pariksha-record.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: "Pariksha Pe Charcha" registrations blew past last year's record. Modi fever (or exam stress) is clearly still a thing.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another year, another registration record shattered for "Pariksha Pe Charcha" (PPC) – clocking in at a bonkers 4.3 crore! Last year's 3.53 crore, which earned a Guinness World Record, now looks like chillar change.</p>
<p>Apparently, everyone wants a piece of Modi's exam advice. Registrations closed January 29th. Stude...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/pariksha-record.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Thieves Busted: Stolen Loot Recovered in Vashi</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-theft-arrests.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Three thieves are in NMMC lockup after a Vashi bust. Police recovered stolen jewellery and appliances – a bad day for crime, a good day for justice (finally!).</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Vashi police station just notched a win. Three individuals are cooling their heels after getting pinched for a string of thefts across the node. Forget cat burglars, these guys were hitting houses and making off with anything they could carry.</p>
<p>Acting on a tip-off, the ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-theft-arrests.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>