<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>Tribal Man Arrested for Marrying, Assaulting Minor</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-25/minor-marriage-assault-panvel.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A tribal man in Navi Mumbai was arrested for marrying and assaulting a minor. Seriously, what is wrong with people?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Panvel Taluka Police Station arrested a 22-year-old man from Tembhode village. He's accused of marrying a 17-year-old girl and then, unbelievably, assaulting her. The FIR (First Information Report) was filed after the victim's family reported the incident.</p>
<p>The charges are serious. They fall under the Protection of C...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-25</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-25/minor-marriage-assault-panvel.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Fire Engulfs Taloja Factory; No Injuries Reported</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-25/taloja-factory-fire.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A factory in Taloja MIDC went up in flames this morning. Thankfully, nobody got hurt. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another day, another fire in Navi Mumbai's industrial heartland. This time, it was a factory in Taloja MIDC that decided to spontaneously combust. The cause? Still unknown, but knowing our luck, it'll be something spectacularly mundane like faulty wiring.</p>
<p>The blaze broke out around 7:00 AM. Firefighters from Taloja and Kharghar rushed to the sc...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-25</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-25/taloja-factory-fire.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>L&T's Massive Green Data Center Lands in Navi Mumbai</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-25/lt-data-center.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: L&amp;T Vyoma just fired up a 40 MW, AI-ready, green data center in Navi Mumbai. Finally, something green that isn't just another patch of sad grass struggling in Sector 17.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T) just plugged in a colossal 40 MW data center. This isn't your uncle's dusty server room; it's built for the AI future, powered by green energy. We're talking serious processing power.</p>
<p>Located somewhere in Navi Mumbai (they're bei...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-25</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-25/lt-data-center.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Mahape MIDC Chemical Blaze: Panic, Smoke, Chaos</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-25/mahape-midc-fire.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A major fire ripped through a chemical company in Mahape MIDC. Expect delays and a lot of finger-pointing about safety protocols.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Mahape MIDC turned into a smoke show this morning after a massive fire erupted at a chemical company. Think apocalyptic movie scene, but with more traffic.</p>
<p>Initial reports suggest the blaze started around 8:00 AM at a facility in Sector A. The exact cause is still under investigation, but eyewitnesses ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-25</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-25/mahape-midc-fire.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>KYC Scam Busted: ₹2 Crore Swiped!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/kyc-scam-busted.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Cops busted a KYC scam ring operating out of Jharkhand and West Bengal. They stole ₹2 crore...the nerve of these guys!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Navi Mumbai's cybercrime unit just took down a gang of digital bandits. Turns out, those KYC update requests weren't so innocent after all.</p>
<p>Four people are cooling their heels in jail right now, thanks to the Nerul police. They allegedly ran a nationwide KYC scam, tricking people into handing over their bank deta...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-24</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/kyc-scam-busted.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NMMC Chief's Salary: High Court Threatens Action</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/nmmc-salary-threat.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The Bombay High Court is tired of waiting and warned they'll stop the NMMC Commissioner's paycheck. Finally, someone's holding them accountable for something around here.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Bombay High Court is not messing around. Fed up with delays, justices issued a warning: the Navi Mumbai Municipal Commissioner's salary is on the chopping block. It's about time.</p>
<p>Specifics on <em>why</em> the court is fuming are still emerging, but it's rela...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-24</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/nmmc-salary-threat.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>TCS building massive data center in Navi Mumbai.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/tcs-data-center.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: TCS wants to build a huge 120 MW data center in Navi Mumbai with AWS and OpenAI. Finally, something cool is coming to Navi Mumbai that isn't just another apartment building.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>TCS is reportedly planning a massive 120 MW data center in our backyard. They're looking to partner with Amazon Web Services (AWS) and OpenAI. Think of the possibilities!</p>
<p>The project is expected to boost TCS's cloud computing and AI capabilities. The location...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-24</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/tcs-data-center.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>₹1 Land Grab Near Airport? TTD Gets Sweet Deal</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/TTD-land-deal.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Government gifted prime land near Navi Mumbai Airport to TTD (Tirumala Tirupati Devasthanams) for peanuts. Is this development or daylight robbery?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>So, <em>this</em> is how it's done. The state cabinet just gifted prime real estate near the upcoming Navi Mumbai International Airport to the Tirumala Tirupati Devasthanams (TTD) for a cool ₹1 per square meter. Yes, you read that right. </p>
<p>The plot, a juicy 20,000 square meters in Ulwe...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-24</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/TTD-land-deal.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai, Mumbai Chiefs' Pay on the Line Over Air</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/hc-threatens-pay.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The High Court is big mad about Navi Mumbai and Mumbai's air pollution. If things don't improve, top officials might not get paid. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Bombay High Court is playing hardball. They're threatening to withhold the salaries of top dogs in both Mumbai and Navi Mumbai over the never-ending air pollution saga. Someone finally had enough of breathing fumes.</p>
<p>The court's order came down on [DATE - <em>insert date of order from source artic...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-24</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/hc-threatens-pay.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>₹74 Lakh Share Trading Scam Hits Navi Mumbai</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/share-scam-panvel.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Panvel resident lost ₹74.6 lakh in a share trading scam. Turns out, dreams of quick riches are still a great way to lose a fortune.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another day, another Navi Mumbaikar fleeced by the siren song of easy money. This time, a Panvel resident got hooked by a fraudulent share trading scheme, ultimately losing ₹74.6 lakh.</p>
<p>The victim, lured by promises of high returns, initially invested small amounts. The scammers then showed fake pro...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-24</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-24/share-scam-panvel.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>CBD Belapur Gets Colorful: Recycled Benches Boosted</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-23/belapur-bench-boost.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Volunteers painted 35 recycled plastic benches in CBD Belapur. Turns out, trash <em>can</em> be treasure, especially when it's Instagrammable.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>CBD Belapur's getting a splash of color, and it's all thanks to recycled plastic. Forget drab grey concrete – we're talking vibrant public seating made from the stuff nobody wants.</p>
<p>As part of the Navi Mumbai Plastic and E-Waste Recyclothon, a crew of volunteers transformed 35 benches near ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-23</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-23/belapur-bench-boost.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>₹2.1 Billion Bet on Navi Mumbai's Future</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-23/navi-mumbai-investment.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: ASK Property Fund just dropped ₹2.1 billion into Navi Mumbai real estate. Is this the start of something huge, or just another Tuesday in the satellite city?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Someone just made a <em>massive</em> down payment on Navi Mumbai's future. ASK Property Fund, known for throwing serious cash at real estate, just invested ₹2.1 billion in a residential project. The lucky developer? Paradigm Ventures.</p>
<p>Specifics are still trickling in, but th...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-23</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-23/navi-mumbai-investment.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>RCB Women Win! GG Women Choke in Navi Mumbai</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-23/rcb-women-win.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: RCB Women finally won a match in Navi Mumbai! GG Women somehow managed to snatch defeat from the jaws of victory. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Okay, RCB Women fans, you can breathe. They finally did it. After a string of losses that made us question reality, they actually won a game at the DY Patil Stadium today. And against GG Women, no less.</p>
<p>GG Women looked set to cruise after setting a target that felt like a stroll in Sector 17. But then, things went fu...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-23</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-23/rcb-women-win.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>₹75 Lakh Stock Scam Hits Ex-Steel Exec</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-22/stock-scam-vashi.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A retired steel company exec in Navi Mumbai got fleeced for ₹75 lakh in an online stock scam. The stock market: still a great way to lose your money.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Sector 17, Vashi, became the latest ground zero for online financial crime. A former assistant general manager of a steel company got duped out of ₹75 lakh. The con? An online stock market trading scheme, naturally.</p>
<p>The victim, whose name is being withheld because, well, embarrassme...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-22</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-22/stock-scam-vashi.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai to get a Woman Mayor!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-22/woman-mayor-navimumbai.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Navi Mumbai is among 15 Maharashtra cities reserving mayoral posts for women. About time, honestly.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Get ready for a shakeup at NMMC headquarters! The state government just announced that Navi Mumbai, along with Pune, Nagpur, and Nashik, will have a woman mayor. Finally.</p>
<p>This isn't just about "girl power" (eye roll). The reservation applies to 29 municipal corporations across Maharashtra. The move is part of a larger effort to, yo...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-22</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-22/woman-mayor-navimumbai.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Power Bills About to Get Even MORE Annoying</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-21/power-bill-hike.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Draft energy policy suggests linking power tariffs to inflation and reducing cross-subsidies. Prepare for even more creative ways to save electricity (or just move to Lonavala). </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Hate your electricity bill? Get ready for round two. Some new draft policy is floating around that wants to link power tariffs to inflation. Meaning: when things get more expensive, <em>your electricity bill does too</em>. </p>
<p>And it doesn't stop there. The...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-21</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-21/power-bill-hike.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NMMC Election Results: Your New Corporators Are...</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-21/nmmc-election-results.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The NMMC election results are in, so get ready for some new faces running our city. Did your ward get someone competent, or just another guy who'll rename a chowk?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The final list of winning candidates from the BJP, Shiv Sena (UBT), MNS, and others is out. Sector 1's party scene is about to get a whole lot more interesting.</p>
<p>So, who's in? Check News18 for the full rundown. We're not going to list every single name; that's what inte...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-21</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-21/nmmc-election-results.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New Navi Mumbai Airport: Hits and Misses</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-21/nmia-first-look.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The new Navi Mumbai airport has some good features, but also some problems, typical of infrastructure projects here. It's shiny, but is it actually convenient?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>So, Condé Nast Traveller India took a look at the new Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA), and, surprise, surprise, it's not all sunshine and imported sand. While the architecture looks impressive, and some of the tech is actually kinda cool, the report suggests some serious...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-21</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-21/nmia-first-look.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BJP Sweeps NMMC Elections: Opposition Crushed</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-20/bjp-nmmc-win.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The BJP dominated the 2026 NMMC elections. Turns out, people <em>do</em> like flyovers and promises of more development. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>The saffron wave crashed over Navi Mumbai. The BJP steamrolled the competition in yesterday's NMMC elections, securing a majority that even their most optimistic supporters didn't predict. Forget a close contest; this was a demolition.</p>
<p>Early results trickled in from the polling centers near Nerul's Seawoods Gr...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-20</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-20/bjp-nmmc-win.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>CISF Cyclathon: Navi Mumbai gets sweaty, eco-friendly visit</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-20/cisf-cyclathon-mumbai.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: CISF cyclists are rolling into Mumbai on February 11th as part of a massive coastal ride. Expect spandex and maybe some sore bums.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Get ready to dodge some lycra! The Central Industrial Security Force (CISF) is bringing its "Cyclathon 2026" to our fair city. We're picturing a peloton of very serious cyclists hitting the streets.</p>
<p>They're slated to arrive in Mumbai around February 11th. After battling headwinds and questionable coas...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-20</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-20/cisf-cyclathon-mumbai.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>