<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>Mercedes stop yields ₹16 Lakh stash</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-cash-seizure.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: ₹16.16 Lakh in unmarked bills were pulled from a Mercedes in Vashi. Election season is here, and suddenly everyone is getting frisked.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The NMMC's election watchdogs had a busy lunch hour yesterday. At 12:35 PM, a Mercedes-Benz cruising through Vashi got the tap on the window. Turns out, it wasn't carrying groceries.</p>
<p>Instead, officials found ₹16.16 Lakh stashed inside. No immediate explanation was offered. No arrests made, yet. Ju...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-cash-seizure.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Election Noise Pollution: Politicians' Fireworks Anger Navi Mumbaikars</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/election-noise-fireworks.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Politicians are blasting music and setting off fireworks for the election, despite the already terrible air quality. Are they actually trying to make us hate them?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The election season's here, and with it, the return of the politicians' favorite hobby: annoying everyone. According to a Reddit post on r/NaviMumbai, the politicians are not just blasting music, but setting off firecrackers too. This is happening despite the fact that the AQ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/election-noise-fireworks.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Koparkhairane Kids Form Human Chain for Votes</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/koparkhairane-human-chain.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Over 1,100 Koparkhairane students created a human chain to promote voter awareness. Honestly, if kids can do this, adults have no excuse not to vote.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Koparkhairane saw a heartwarming display of civic responsibility this week, with students, teachers, and parents joining hands (literally) for voter awareness. Forget rallies; these kids are doing it right.</p>
<p>The human chain, organized under the Systematic Voters' Education and Electo...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/koparkhairane-human-chain.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>