<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Airport: Now open all night, every night.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-02-01/nmia-24-7.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Navi Mumbai Airport is now running 24/7. Finally, you can fly out at 3 AM if that's your thing (or your only option).</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Good news for the night owls (and the chronically delayed): Navi Mumbai's airport is officially a 24/7 operation. Forget those awkward red-eye flights from Mumbai; now you can take the Panvel local and fly out of NMIA whenever you please.</p>
<p>The shift to round-the-clock operations has been surprisingly smooth, accord...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-02-01</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-02-01/nmia-24-7.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Fake Trading App Scam Busted; Four in Jail</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-02-01/trading-app-scam.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Navi Mumbai police arrested four for a trading app scam. Honestly, who <em>still</em> falls for this?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Cyber Crime division of the Navi Mumbai police just took down a ring of scammers peddling bogus trading apps. Four guys are cooling their heels in the lockup after allegedly fleecing victims across the city. This isn't exactly rocket science, people. </p>
<p>The con went something like this: Victims got bombarded with ads for tradin...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-02-01</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-02-01/trading-app-scam.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sunetra Pawar Gets Deputy CM Gig; Andrew Photo Surfaces</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-31/deputy-cm-andrew.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Sunetra Pawar is now deputy CM; Prince Andrew's Epstein connections get messier. This week is <em>wild</em>.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>So, Sunetra Pawar got sworn in as Maharashtra's Deputy CM. Just days after her husband's death. Politics, eh? Wonder what Ajit Pawar thinks of all this, considering the family drama is thicker than Kharghar traffic during peak hours.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Epstein files just dropped <em>more</em> bombs. This time? A photo of Princ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-31</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-31/deputy-cm-andrew.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sunetra Pawar Sworn In: Ajit's Seat Filled</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-31/sunetra-pawar-dcm.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Sunetra Pawar is the new deputy CM, replacing her late husband, Ajit. Well, that was fast. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Raj Bhavan saw another oath-taking ceremony this weekend. This time, it was Sunetra Pawar stepping into the deputy CM's chair. Acharya Devvrat did the honors Saturday evening.</p>
<p>Sunetra Pawar takes over from her husband, Ajit, who, <em>checks notes</em>, tragically died mid-week in that suspicious plane crash. The speed of this successio...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-31</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-31/sunetra-pawar-dcm.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Paver Block Murders: Life Sentence Finally Handed Down</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-31/paver-block-verdict.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Panvel resident got a life sentence for killing two friends with a paver block back in 2017. Justice finally arrived, seven years late and with a healthy dose of closure for the victims' families.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Seven years after the brutal murder of two friends in Panvel, a court finally delivered its verdict. The accused, a local resident, will spend the rest of his natural life behind bars.</p>
<p>The victims, discovered near a desolate stretch o...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-31</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-31/paver-block-verdict.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Airport: International Flights by 2026?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-31/nm-airport-2026.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Navi Mumbai Airport aims for international flights in early 2026 after getting the green light for night flights. If you believe that, I have a bridge (or should I say, skywalk) to sell you.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Finally, some potentially good news about that airport we've all been hearing about forever. CEO Bansal says they're aiming to launch international operations in the first quarter of fiscal year 2027. That's basically early 2026 for those of us who ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-31</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-31/nm-airport-2026.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Gold scammer targets retired engineer in Navi Mumbai.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-31/gold-scam-panvel.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A con artist, known for past gold-related scams, allegedly swindled a retired civil engineer. Victim lost ₹2.87 lakh after believing the suspect's fake gold story, <em>again</em>. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Panvel resident is probably kicking himself right now. He fell for <em>the oldest trick in the book</em>...again. Police say the suspect, already known for similar scams, sweet-talked the retiree into believing he had a stash of cheap gold. </p>
<p>The vi...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-31</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-31/gold-scam-panvel.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Airport Metro: Navi Mumbai to Mumbai in 30 Minutes?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-30/airport-metro-link.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A new Metro line will link Navi Mumbai and Mumbai airports. Finally, maybe you won't need to sell a kidney to pay for a slightly faster commute. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Forget those two-hour traffic crawls to the airport. A new "Gold Line" Metro is in the works, promising to slash travel time between Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA) and Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj International Airport (CSMIA) to a breezy 30 minutes. About damn time.</p>
<p>The Econom...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-30</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-30/airport-metro-link.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Metro to Navi Mumbai Airport Finally Approved. Seriously.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-30/airport-metro-approved.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The Maharashtra cabinet greenlit the long-awaited metro link connecting Mumbai and Navi Mumbai airports. Maybe this time it'll actually happen; don't hold your breath.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The ₹12,700 Crore project aims to directly connect the upcoming Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA) to the existing Mumbai airport, Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj International Airport (CSMIA). The Raigad Collectorate is already acquiring land for the Taloja to NMIA sec...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-30</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-30/airport-metro-approved.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Accountant Duped: ₹1.3 Crore Gone in Fraud</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-29/accountant-fraud-crore.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Navi Mumbai accountant got fleeced for ₹1.3 crore in an insurance scam. Turns out "guaranteed returns" are only guaranteed to empty your bank account.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another day, another fraud in NMMC. This time, an accountant from Sector 17, Vashi, got conned out of a staggering ₹1.3 crore. The bait? Sweet promises of sky-high returns on an insurance policy.</p>
<p>The fraudsters, now booked by the cybercrime cell, spun a web of lies. They lured th...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-29</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-29/accountant-fraud-crore.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Metro: Finally, a Green Light!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-29/metro-approved-finally.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The state government approved the extended Navi Mumbai Metro lines. We're cautiously optimistic; let's see if they actually build it this time.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Maharashtra government has <em>finally</em> given the go-ahead for expanding the Navi Mumbai Metro. After years of delays that would make even CIDCO blush, Lines 2, 3, and 4 are supposedly ready to roll. The ₹15,000-Crore project aims to connect every corner of this sprawling city.</p>
<p>Li...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-29</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-29/metro-approved-finally.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Finally! Metro to Navi Mumbai Airport Approved.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-29/metro-airport-approved.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The state cabinet greenlit the 35km Metro Line 8 connecting Mumbai Airport to NMIA. About time somebody figured out how to connect the airports.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>After years of talk, the Metro Line 8 is actually happening. The cabinet waved its magic wand (read: signed off on paperwork) for the ₹15,000 Crore project. Expect a slightly less hellish commute to catch those early morning flights.</p>
<p>The route will stretch 35km, linking Chhatrapati Shiva...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-29</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-29/metro-airport-approved.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Finally! Mumbai Airport Metro Link Approved. Praise Ganpati!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-29/airport-metro-approved.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The state cabinet greenlit the Nerul-Uran metro extension to the new airport. Now, maybe we can <em>actually</em> fly somewhere on time.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>So, it's official. The Maha Vikas Aghadi Cabinet, fresh off their Ganpati holiday, approved the ₹5,600 Crore metro link to the Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA) yesterday. Someone deserves a modak.</p>
<p>The 27-kilometer extension of Metro Line 1 (Nerul to Uran) will connect Kharkopar to the ai...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-29</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-29/airport-metro-approved.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Airport Metro: Finally, a train that flies.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-29/airport-metro-finally.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The new metro line will directly connect Mumbai to Navi Mumbai Airport. We're cautiously optimistic, but also bracing for the usual delays.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Forget battling Palm Beach Road traffic. Finally, there's a light at the end of the tunnel. A metro line will <em>finally</em> link Mumbai directly to Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA).</p>
<p>Think about it: Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj International Airport (CSMIA) to NMIA without wanting to...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-29</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-29/airport-metro-finally.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>₹18,000 Crore Metro: Airport to Airport!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-28/airport-metro-link.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A new 35km metro line will connect Mumbai and Navi Mumbai Airports. Finally, some good news amidst never ending construction.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Finally! A reason to be (cautiously) optimistic. The City and Industrial Development Corporation (CIDCO) is building a 35-km metro line that will directly link both airports. Think fewer rickshaw rides and less Palm Beach Road rage.</p>
<p>The ₹18,000 crore project aims to make travel between Chhatrapati Shivaji ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-28</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-28/airport-metro-link.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Airport Metro Approved: Finally Some Good News</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-28/airport-metro-approved.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The state cabinet greenlit the Mumbai-Navi Mumbai Airport metro link. About damn time, honestly. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Thank the heavens, the Mumbai-Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA) metro link is finally happening. The cabinet gave it the thumbs-up, so maybe, just maybe, we can stop relying on that overcrowded highway.</p>
<p>The new line will connect CSMIA (Mumbai Airport) to NMIA (Navi Mumbai Airport), promising sweet relief for anyone who’s battl...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-28</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-28/airport-metro-approved.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Airport Commute Slashed? Metro Promises Relief.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-28/airport-metro-relief.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Mumbai's building a ₹22,862 crore metro line to speed up airport trips. Finally, a possible escape from Palm Beach Road's parking lot.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Indian Express says that the new metro line aims to cut travel time to Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj International Airport from 75 minutes to just 30. Imagine actually making a flight without the usual heart-stopping sprint from Vashi.</p>
<p>This isn't some pipe dream from CIDCO; it's an actual plan w...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-28</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-28/airport-metro-relief.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Naik declares war on Shinde. Navi Mumbai rumble?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-27/naik-shinde-feud.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Ganesh Naik, once a big shot, is now gunning for CM Shinde's political scalp. Expect fireworks (and maybe some traffic jams) in the run-up to the next election.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Ganesh Naik isn't happy. The former NCP heavyweight and ex-minister has declared open season on Chief Minister Eknath Shinde, promising to "wipe out" Shinde's influence, according to <em>The Indian Express</em>. Ouch.</p>
<p>Naik, a dominant figure in Navi Mumbai politics for de...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-27</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-27/naik-shinde-feud.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tata's ₹1 Lakh Crore AI City Coming to NM!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-27/tata-ai-city.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Tata Group is dropping a ₹1 Lakh Crore AI Innovation City near Navi Mumbai. Get ready for robots, or at least a lot more traffic.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Alright, buckle up, folks! Tata Group just announced they're building a massive AI Innovation City right in our backyard. We're talking a ₹1 Lakh Crore investment – that's enough to fix the potholes on Sion-Panvel highway for, like, a century. </p>
<p>Specifics are still hazy, but we're told it will be somewh...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-27</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-27/tata-ai-city.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Shiv Sena Rally: Vaidya Breaks Rules, Gets Booked</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-27/vaidya-rally-booked.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Milind Vaidya, Shiv Sena (UBT) corporator, got booked for holding a rally without permission. Rules are for everyone else, apparently.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another day, another politician thinking the rules don't apply to them. This time, it's Milind Vaidya, who decided his victory was so important, he'd ignore the little detail of, you know, getting permission for a rally.</p>
<p>Mahim police said “no” to Vaidya’s party on January 18 because of some rules ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-27</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-27/vaidya-rally-booked.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>