<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>Metro Line 1: Trials Done, Ready to Roll?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trials-done.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Metro Line 1 oscillation trials wrapped up successfully. Is anyone <em>actually</em> surprised things went smoothly for once? </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Finally, some good news on the Metro front. Oscillation trials for Line 1 (CBD Belapur to Pendhar) concluded yesterday. That means we're one step closer to <em>maybe</em> having a functioning metro system. </p>
<p>The trials, overseen by the Research Designs and Standards Organisation (RDSO), involved testing th...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trials-done.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Airport Name Fight: More Protests Coming?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-name-protest.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: All-party meeting today will decide on future protests over the naming of Navi Mumbai Airport. Prepare for more traffic jams and shouting matches, folks.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The naming drama at Navi Mumbai Airport is heading for Act II. An all-party meeting is scheduled today to decide whether to ramp up protests over the airport's proposed name: D. B. Patil International Airport.</p>
<p>For those just tuning in, the state government wants to name it after...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-name-protest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kharghar, Ulwe: No Water This Weekend</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-water-cut.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Kharghar, Ulwe, and Dronagiri are going dry this weekend due to pipeline repairs. Guess it's time to finally befriend that neighbor with the RO filter.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Forget Sunday brunch plans. NMMC is shutting off the water supply to Kharghar, Ulwe, and Dronagiri from Sunday, starting 10 AM. The tap will run dry until Monday, 10 AM. That’s a full 24 hours of strategic water conservation. </p>
<p>The official reason? “Urgent repairs” to the Bhokarpad...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-water-cut.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cop Vanishes, Claims Corruption by Senior</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-graft.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Navi Mumbai police officer is missing after a letter surfaced accusing his superior of corruption; the wife has filed a complaint. Sounds like someone watched too much 'Gangs of Wasseypur'.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>It's getting spicy in the Navi Mumbai police force. A police constable from the NRI Coastal police station is MIA, and things are getting weirder by the minute. </p>
<p>The constable's wife filed a missing person report after he didn't return home....</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-graft.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COVID Hits Navi Mumbai School: 18 Infected</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/covid-school-nerul.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Eighteen students at a Nerul school tested positive for COVID-19. Guess those masks weren't optional after all. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Panic at the podium. Eighteen students at a Nerul school are down with COVID. The news broke late yesterday after a routine check at the Ryan International School in Sector 44. </p>
<p>The NMMC health department scrambled to contain the outbreak. Parents received frantic calls and directives to keep their kids home. Contact t...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/covid-school-nerul.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Airport Name Fight: More Protests Incoming?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-name-protests.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: All-party meeting today will decide whether to launch further protests against the naming of Navi Mumbai Airport. Expect drama, because when <em>doesn't</em> Navi Mumbai have drama?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The naming saga of Navi Mumbai International Airport continues. An all-party meeting is scheduled today to decide whether to escalate protests. At stake? The name: D.B. Patil International Airport – a proposal that's ignited passions across Panvel and beyond...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-name-protests.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Political Parties Have Your Number: You're Not Paranoid</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/political-call-spam.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Navi Mumbaikars are getting spammed by political calls. Where did they get your number? Probably everywhere.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Are you getting daily calls from politicians you've never heard of? Welcome to the club. Residents across Navi Mumbai are reporting a sudden surge in campaign calls and SMS blasts, leaving many wondering how their contact information ended up on some party's database.</p>
<p>The answer? Data brokers, leaky databases, and the fine...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/political-call-spam.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Election Noise Pollution: Navi Mumbai's Politicians Just Don't Care</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/election-noise-pollution.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Politicians are blasting music and setting off firecrackers during the election, despite terrible air quality. Apparently, common sense isn't a prerequisite for running for office in this town.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Navi Mumbai residents are losing their minds over non-stop election noise. According to one fed-up resident in Kharghar Sector 35, the non-stop music is bad enough, but the firecrackers are next-level dumb.</p>
<p>"Do they not realize how bad the...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/election-noise-pollution.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Student's Scholarship Vanishes in ₹2 Lakh Scam</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/scholarship-scam.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A student lost ₹2 lakh, including scholarship money, to cyber fraud. Seriously, can't anyone keep our money safe?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The dream of higher education just got a lot more expensive for one Nerul student. A cyber fraud wiped out ₹2 lakh from their account, including a hefty chunk of scholarship funds earmarked for tuition at SIES College.</p>
<p>The scam played out with classic simplicity. Posing as a bank representative, the fraudster called t...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/scholarship-scam.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NMMC: Borrow a Book, Skip the Boredom</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-bus-books.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: NMMC installs mini-libraries at bus stops. Finally, something useful from the corporation that isn't a pothole.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Tired of doom-scrolling while waiting for the 520 LTD? Navi Mumbai Municipal Corporation (NMMC) heard your silent screams and installed mini-libraries at bus shelters across the city.</p>
<p>Imagine this: you're at the Nerul Sector 21 bus stop, already late. Instead of watching another Instagram reel, you can grab a Chetan Bha...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-bus-books.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Creep Creates Fake Insta Account, Posts Teen's Pics</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/insta-creep-arrested.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A pervert made a fake Instagram profile to post obscene content of a teenager. Turns out, some people are still the worst, even in Navi Mumbai.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The cyber cell nabbed a 21-year-old from Ghansoli for creating a fake Instagram account and uploading obscene content of a minor. Apparently, people still do this kind of garbage. The guy's been remanded to police custody until the 27th. Good.</p>
<p>The victim, a 17-year-old from Airoli, notice...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/insta-creep-arrested.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Hanuman Chalisa vs. H&M: Protest Erupts</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/hm-protest-seawoods.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Hindu group protested an H&amp;M ad they found offensive. Next time, maybe stick to selling clothes, guys.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Outside the H&amp;M showroom in Seawoods Grand Central Mall, things got spicy this afternoon. A group chanting the Hanuman Chalisa gathered to protest what they deemed an “offensive” advertisement displayed in the store's window.</p>
<p>What was the ad? Details are hazy, but it was apparently enough to trigger the ire of a local pr...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/hm-protest-seawoods.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Metro: Trial Run Success!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trial-success.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: CIDCO ran a metro trial from Pendhar to Central Park. Good news if you like trains; bad news if you hate construction.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Finally! The Navi Mumbai Metro <em>might</em> actually happen. CIDCO successfully completed a trial run on Line 1, from Pendhar in Sector 12 to Central Park in Sector 23. This isn't a drill (probably).</p>
<p>The train trundled along the 11-km stretch, a tiny victory after years of delays. Remember when they said it wou...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trial-success.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COVID Hits Nerul School: 18 Test Positive</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nerul-covid-scare.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Eighteen students at a Nerul school tested positive for COVID-19. Remember when we thought we were done with this? Yeah, us too.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Chaos at a Nerul school today after eighteen students tested positive for COVID-19. Parents are, understandably, freaking out. The school, located in Sector 21, is now a containment zone. </p>
<p>The news broke this morning after a routine check-up revealed the cluster. NMMC health officials are on-site, scram...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nerul-covid-scare.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Woman loses ₹45 Lakh in gift scam</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/gift-scam.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Panvel woman got scammed out of ₹45 lakh by believing a fake customs demand. Turns out, online "gifts" are just a great way to lose your life savings.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another day, another ludicrous online scam. This time, a Panvel resident got played for ₹45.91 lakh by crooks promising a valuable gift. Seriously, people, are we still falling for this?</p>
<p>The victim, a resident of sector 6, Panvel, received a WhatsApp message from an unknown numbe...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/gift-scam.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cop Vanishes, Claims Corruption by Top Officer</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-corruption.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Navi Mumbai police officer is missing after a letter surfaced accusing a senior official of corruption. His wife has filed a complaint; this could get messy.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Navi Mumbai police force has a mystery on its hands: one of their own is gone. A police naik (constable), posted in the security department, disappeared this week, leaving behind a letter alleging corruption by a senior officer.</p>
<p>The letter, now in the hands of the Raig...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-corruption.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NMMC: Read a Book, Skip the Traffic</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-books-bus.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: NMMC launched mini-libraries at bus stops. Finally, something to do besides stare blankly at the Panvel bus.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Tired of doomscrolling while waiting for the 520 to Nerul? The NMMC has a solution that doesn't involve more screen time: books. Small, open-air libraries have popped up at bus shelters across the city.</p>
<p>Think of it as a literary pit stop. The initiative, costing ₹10 lakh, stocks each location with a rotating collection of ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-books-bus.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>