<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>BJP Nomination Snafu: NMMC Election Stalled</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-election-halt.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: High Court halts Ward 17A election after BJP candidate's nomination gets tossed. Expect political squabbling and legal maneuvering – because that's how things roll in Navi Mumbai.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The High Court slammed the brakes on the Ward 17A election in the NMMC, all because someone fumbled a BJP nomination. The order came down after the BJP candidate, Tanaji Madhvi's, paperwork got rejected, sparking a legal challenge faster than you can say "elec...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-election-halt.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Mercedes stop yields ₹16 Lakh stash</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-cash-seizure.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: ₹16.16 Lakh in unmarked bills were pulled from a Mercedes in Vashi. Election season is here, and suddenly everyone is getting frisked.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The NMMC's election watchdogs had a busy lunch hour yesterday. At 12:35 PM, a Mercedes-Benz cruising through Vashi got the tap on the window. Turns out, it wasn't carrying groceries.</p>
<p>Instead, officials found ₹16.16 Lakh stashed inside. No immediate explanation was offered. No arrests made, yet. Ju...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-cash-seizure.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1100 Students Chain Themselves to Democracy (Sort Of)</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/student-vote-chain.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Over a thousand students made a human chain to encourage voting in the upcoming NMMC elections. Let's hope they understand the irony of forced participation promoting free will.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Forget flash mobs. The new hotness? Human chains for democracy! 1100 students snaked through Vashi this morning, holding hands to raise awareness for the 2026 NMMC elections.</p>
<p>Organized by the Thane Zilla Parishad, the chain stretched from outside the APMC...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/student-vote-chain.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ward 17A Election Drama: Stayed (Again!)</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/ward-17a-election-stay.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The Ward 17A election is on hold <em>again</em>. Honestly, at this point, just flip a coin. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Another day, another twist in the saga of Ward 17A's election. It's like watching a badly scripted soap opera, but with more paperwork.</p>
<p>Lokshahi English News reports the election is stayed. The exact reasons? Shrouded in the usual bureaucratic fog. This latest delay throws the representation of Sector 2 through 8 (Nerul) into further disa...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/ward-17a-election-stay.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BJP Candidate Back in Navi Mumbai Election Race</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bjp-candidate-reinstated.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The High Court intervened, ordering a BJP candidate's inclusion in the Navi Mumbai civic polls. Bureaucratic blunders almost sidelined a contender, but thankfully, common sense prevailed (sort of).</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Looks like someone's getting a second shot at the NMMC elections. The Bombay High Court just told election officials they messed up. Turns out, a BJP candidate's nomination was wrongly rejected. Oops.</p>
<p>The court's order forces election ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bjp-candidate-reinstated.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Giants crush Warriorz: WPL 2026 Kicks Off!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/giants-win-wpl.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Gujarat Giants defeated UP Warriorz by 10 runs in the opening match of WPL 2026 at the DY Patil Stadium. This victory proves that maybe, just maybe, the next WPL season won't be a total snooze-fest.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Navi Mumbai witnessed a nail-biting start to the Women's Premier League 2026 as the Gujarat Giants edged out the UP Warriorz. The Giants posted a respectable 162, then strangled the Warriorz' chase with tight bowling in the death overs.</p>
...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/giants-win-wpl.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Naik: Shinde Emptied NMMC Coffers</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/shinde-nmmc-funds.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: BJP Minister Ganesh Naik accuses CM Shinde of looting the NMMC treasury during his time as minister. Is anyone actually surprised by this accusation? </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Ganesh Naik is throwing shade (again). This time, the BJP minister is accusing Chief Minister Eknath Shinde of raiding the Navi Mumbai Municipal Corporation's bank account when he was in charge of the Urban Development portfolio.</p>
<p>Naik, never one to mince words, claims Shinde used h...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/shinde-nmmc-funds.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>War of Words: Sena Slams BJP Over Navi Mumbai</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/sena-bjp-feud.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Shiv Sena is accusing a BJP leader of screwing up Navi Mumbai's development. Drama alert: expect more political mudslinging.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The political temperature in Navi Mumbai just cranked up a notch. Shiv Sena (UBT) is going after a local BJP leader, alleging shady dealings in the city's development projects. Buckle up, because this could get messy.</p>
<p>Specifically, the Sena is pointing fingers at irregularities of a BJP leader in planning p...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/sena-bjp-feud.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Dust Devils Shut Down 19 Construction Sites</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/dust-sites-shut.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: NMMC halted work at 19 construction sites and issued warnings to 42 others due to dust pollution violations. Apparently, Navi Mumbai's air quality isn't just 'meh' – it's officially 'shut-down-construction-sites' bad.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The NMMC’s crackdown on construction-related air pollution finally arrived. Nineteen sites across the city found themselves abruptly silenced by stop-work orders. The culprit? Blatant disregard for dust control measures.</...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/dust-sites-shut.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Nerul Landlords Busted: Illegal Rentals to Nigerians</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nerul-illegal-rentals.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Four Nerul landlords are in trouble for renting to eight Nigerians without proper checks. Expect fines and maybe worse.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Nerul's rental market just got interesting. Four landlords in Sector 21 are facing the music after allegedly renting their flats to eight Nigerian nationals without following the rules. Whoops.</p>
<p>The cops say the landlords didn't bother verifying the tenants' documents, violating established procedure. This isn't ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nerul-illegal-rentals.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>MI Demolishes DC: Harmanpreet & Sciver-Brunt Star</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/mi-dc-rout.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Mumbai Indians crushed Delhi Capitals by 50 runs. Another day, another reminder that Mumbai owns this tournament.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Capitals just got schooled. Harmanpreet hammered 55, Nat Sciver-Brunt blasted 32, and MI's bowlers choked the life out of DC's chase. The final score? A brutal 159 for 5 against a paltry 109 for 9.</p>
<p>Harmanpreet's knock wasn't just runs; it was a masterclass in timing, peppered with sixes that landed somewhere near ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/mi-dc-rout.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Ward Election Halted! BJP Candidate Gets Stay.</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/ward-22-election-halt.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Ward 22 will not vote on January 15th. A BJP candidate got a court to put the election on pause; expect a legal battle.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Navi Mumbai election cycle took another wild turn. The Bombay High Court just granted an interim stay, halting the Ward 22 election. This follows a petition filed by a BJP candidate, throwing a wrench into the NMMC's plans.</p>
<p>Details are still emerging, but the core issue revolves around alleged irregularities...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/ward-22-election-halt.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>WPL 2026 Opens: Honey Singh Sets NM On Fire</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-opens-glitz.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: WPL 2026 launched with a star-studded show in Navi Mumbai. Because nothing says 'cricket' like Yo Yo Honey Singh.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The DY Patil Stadium became ground zero for Bollywood flash last night. Jacqueline Fernandez and Yo Yo Honey Singh kicked off the Women's Premier League 2026 opening ceremony. Forget sixes; we got dance moves and questionable lyrics instead.</p>
<p>Sources report deafening cheers (and probable tinnitus) as Honey Singh belted...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-opens-glitz.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BJP Candidate Back in NMMC Election Race</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bjp-candidate-revived.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Bombay High Court revived a BJP candidate's NMMC nomination. Bureaucratic bungling almost sidelined a key player, but the courts said "nah."</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The BJP's Sandeep Thakur is back in the NMMC election ring after the Bombay High Court intervened. Some paperwork snafu threatened to sideline him, but justice (allegedly) prevailed.</p>
<p>Thakur's nomination for Ward 114 (Turbhe) was initially tossed out by the NMMC election officer. Reason? A mi...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/bjp-candidate-revived.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>WPL Mania Returns: Navi Mumbai Gears Up!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-back-mumbai.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The Women's Premier League is back in Navi Mumbai. Expect traffic and cricket fever.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The stands are dusted, the pitches prepped, and the traffic diversions are already in place. The Women's Premier League (WPL) is back, and Navi Mumbai is once again the epicenter of six-smashing, wicket-taking mayhem.</p>
<p>Can MI snag their third title? They're the bookies' favorite, but let's be real, anything can happen when Harmanpreet Kaur steps u...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wpl-back-mumbai.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1100 Students Make Human Chain. Will Anyone Vote?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/human-chain-election.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Over a thousand students linked arms to promote voting in the 2026 NMMC elections. Considering youth apathy, will this stunt actually work, or is it just another photo op?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Mid-day breathlessly reported that 1100 students formed a human chain this week. The goal? To raise awareness for the upcoming Navi Mumbai civic elections.</p>
<p>The chain stretched from the Nerul LP signal all the way to the DY Patil stadium. Seriously, who signed o...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/human-chain-election.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Fights Back to Save Wetlands</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wetlands-rescue-navi-mumbai.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Fed up with disappearing mangroves, Navi Mumbai residents launched a new environmental initiative. Finally, someone is doing something about CIDCO's relentless 'development'.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Anger is brewing in Navi Mumbai. Residents, tired of watching wetlands vanish under concrete, have launched a citizens' movement. Their goal? To protect the city's remaining mangroves, lakes, and vital ecosystems.</p>
<p>The "Save Navi Mumbai's Wetlands" initiative...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/wetlands-rescue-navi-mumbai.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NMMC Hammers 19 Sites for Pollution</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-pollution-crackdown.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: NMMC stopped work at 19 construction sites for flouting pollution rules. Turns out, Navi Mumbai's developers aren't as 'eco-friendly' as their brochures suggest.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Dust chokes Ghansoli. Concrete mixers roar in Nerul. NMMC finally noticed, hitting 19 construction sites with stop-work notices. And get this: a whopping ₹43.25 lakh in fines levied against 173 developers. Because apparently, rules are just suggestions now.</p>
<p>According to ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-pollution-crackdown.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>₹16 Lakh Seized From APMC Trader's Car</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/apmc-cash-seizure.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: NMMC election squad found ₹16 lakh in an APMC trader's Mercedes. Looks like someone forgot that election season means <em>extra</em> scrutiny. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Election season's heating up, and so is the NMMC's vigilance. Yesterday, their flying squad intercepted a Mercedes-Benz near the APMC market, Sector 19, Vashi. Inside? A cool ₹16 lakh in cash, allegedly belonging to an unnamed APMC trader.</p>
<p>The cash was discovered during a routine check. T...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/apmc-cash-seizure.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai: Citizens Fight Back for Nature</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/navi-mumbai-wetlands.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Navi Mumbai residents are uniting to protect the city's mangroves, wetlands, and lakes. Finally, someone's doing something about the vanishing flamingos of Seawoods.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Fed up with concrete devouring every green space, a coalition of Navi Mumbaikars launched a grassroots environmental initiative this week. The goal? To actively protect the remaining mangroves, wetlands, and lakes that define the city's fragile ecosystem.</p>
<p>The group, ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/navi-mumbai-wetlands.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>