<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Metro: Test Run Successful!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-test-success.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: The Navi Mumbai Metro's Pendhar to Central Park line aced its trial run. Maybe we'll actually get to use this thing someday.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Navi Mumbai Metro just took a big step – a successful trial run from Pendhar to Central Park! CIDCO finally gave the green light after what feels like a decade of delays.</p>
<p>The test zipped along the 11-km stretch on Line 1, hitting stations in Sectors 11, 34, and 21. No word yet on when <em>actual</em> se...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-test-success.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Metro Line 1: Trials Complete!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trials-done.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Metro Line 1 oscillation trials are donezo. Get ready for slightly less chaotic commutes, maybe.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Line 1 of the Navi Mumbai Metro just cleared a hurdle. Oscillation trials – basically, testing how the train bounces around – wrapped up successfully this week.</p>
<p>CRISIL (that's the Railway's safety watchdog) signed off on the reports. This means Line 1 is closer than ever to actually carrying people.</p>
<p>But don't hold your breath j...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trials-done.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kharghar, Ulwe, Dronagiri: No Water Sunday</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/no-water-sunday.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: NMMC is shutting off the water to Kharghar, Ulwe, and Dronagiri on Sunday. Stock up on H2O now, or prepare for a very dry day, you parched landlubbers.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Yep, you read that right. No water. The NMMC water supply will be disrupted this Sunday, thanks to "urgent repairs" at the Hetawane Dam. Residents of Kharghar, Ulwe, and Dronagiri are going to be real thirsty. Brace yourselves, folks.</p>
<p>The shutdown starts at 10:00 AM and is <em>sch...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/no-water-sunday.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cop Goes Missing, Corruption Letter Surfaces</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cop-missing.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Navi Mumbai police officer is missing after a letter accusing a senior of corruption surfaced. Someone's career is about to end VERY badly.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Navi Mumbai police force has a mystery on its hands. Inspector Abhay Kurundkar of the NRI Coastal police station vanished this week, leaving behind a letter alleging widespread corruption within the department.</p>
<p>Kurundkar's wife filed a missing person complaint after he failed to return ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cop-missing.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COVID Returns: 18 Students Test Positive</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/covid-school-nerul.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: 18 students at a Nerul school tested positive for COVID-19, raising concerns about a new wave. Remember when we thought 2020 was over? Good times.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Panic at Ryan International School in Nerul after nearly twenty students caught COVID. Parents are scrambling, and attendance numbers look set to plummet faster than the monsoon drains overflow.</p>
<p>The outbreak occurred in Sector 21. Contact tracing is underway, according to NMMC official...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/covid-school-nerul.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Hanuman Sena to Brand: Cover That Ad!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/hanuman-sena-protest.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A pro-Hindu group protested an ad outside a clothing store in Vashi. They think it's disrespectful to Hinduism; the brand is staying quiet, probably hoping it blows over.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Hanuman Sena showed up outside a clothing store in Vashi Sector 17 yesterday, and they weren't there to shop. The problem? A promotional image they're calling offensive to Hindu beliefs. The ad features, according to Sena members, imagery that clashes with their re...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/hanuman-sena-protest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NMMC's Book Swap: Read On The Go!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-books.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: NMMC launched mini-libraries at bus stops so you can read while waiting. Finally, something actually useful from the NMMC.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Forget doom-scrolling on Instagram. Now you can pretend to be cultured while waiting for the 520 from Kharghar at Sector 14. The NMMC installed mini-libraries at bus shelters across the city this week.</p>
<p>Shelters now stock everything from Chetan Bhagat to, allegedly, some actual literature. The idea is simple: ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-books.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Airport Name Fight: More Protests Coming?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-name-protests.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Protests over the Navi Mumbai airport's name might ramp up today after a key meeting. Expect more roadblocks and shouting matches; business as usual in Panvel.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The naming drama at the Navi Mumbai International Airport is far from over. Today's meeting of various groups will decide whether to unleash another wave of protests. Remember the last one? Chaos near Panvel station, burning tires, the whole nine yards.</p>
<p>At the core: a batt...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-name-protests.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Metro Line 1: Trials Done!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-line-trials.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Metro Line 1 oscillation trials are complete, so expect to see a lot more of those colourful trains rolling around. Maybe now we'll finally get to use it before 2030.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Those bright yellow Metro trains zipping around are <em>finally</em> getting closer to carrying actual people. The oscillation trials for Line 1, connecting Belapur to Pendhar, wrapped up this week.</p>
<p>What does that even <em>mean</em>? Basically, the Commissioner of M...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-line-trials.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Gifts Gone Wrong: Woman Scammed ₹46 Lakh</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cyber-gift-scam.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Panvel woman lost ₹45.91 lakh in a "gift" cyber scam. Seriously, folks, if someone offers you free money online, run the other way. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>The oldest trick in the book just got a high-tech makeover. A 58-year-old woman from Panvel's Khanda Colony got rinsed for a staggering ₹45.91 lakh by online scammers promising a gift. It started with a friendly message and ended with an empty bank account. </p>
<p>The fraudsters, posing as generous gift...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/cyber-gift-scam.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NMMC's Book Nook: Read While You Wait</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-book-nook.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: NMMC launches mini-libraries at bus stops. Finally, something to do while your bus is late.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Tired of staring at traffic while waiting for the 525 LTD? The NMMC has a solution: books! They're installing mini-libraries at bus stops across the city. Finally, some good news for commuters.</p>
<p>Imagine this: You're at the Nerul bus depot, late for work (again). Instead of doom-scrolling, you grab a book. Not just any book – maybe a thrille...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/nmmc-book-nook.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Student fleeced ₹2 Lakh in Scholarship Scam</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/scholarship-scam.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Navi Mumbai student lost ₹2 lakh to cyber fraud, including scholarship funds. Seriously, people, the internet is still trying to steal your money. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>A Panvel student's bank account just got lighter by ₹2 lakh, thanks to some smooth-talking cyber crooks. The victim, a bright spark trying to make ends meet, saw a chunk of their scholarship money vanish into thin air. That's right, they targeted a student's scholarship. Scum.</p>
<p>The s...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/scholarship-scam.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Fake Insta Account Nightmare: Teen Targeted in Vashi</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/fake-insta-arrest.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Vashi creep made a fake Insta account of a teen and posted nasty stuff. Cops caught him, proving the internet isn't as anonymous as losers think.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The internet got a little less anonymous this week after Vashi police busted a guy for creating a fake Instagram account and posting obscene content of a teenage girl. Think twice before you be a jerk online, kids.</p>
<p>The accused, a 23-year-old from Sector 17, allegedly swiped photos of ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/fake-insta-arrest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Metro: Trial Run Success!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trial-success.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: CIDCO's metro whizzed from Pendhar to Central Park flawlessly. Finally, something in this city works on the first try.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Guess what actually worked for once? CIDCO finally did a successful trial run of the Navi Mumbai Metro, Line 1, from Pendhar to Central Park this morning. Yes, you read that right. No delays (this time!).</p>
<p>The train smoothly sailed through the 11 stations, proving that maybe, just maybe, we'll be able to ditch the...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trial-success.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Student Scammed: ₹2 Lakh Gone, Scholarship Vanished</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/student-scam-nerul.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Nerul student lost ₹2 lakh, including scholarship funds, to a cyber scam. Turns out, even the smartest kids can get played, and these scammers are getting way too good at this.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The dream of paying for college just turned into a digital nightmare for a student from Nerul's Sector 21. They got fleeced for ₹2 lakh in a sophisticated online scam, a chunk of which was hard-earned scholarship money. Irony? We've got bucketloads.</p>
<p>The ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/student-scam-nerul.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cop Goes Missing, Corruption Letter Surfaces</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-corruption.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Navi Mumbai police officer is missing after a letter accusing a senior officer of corruption surfaced. This whole thing is messier than Kharghar during peak hour.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Navi Mumbai police force has a mystery on its hands, and it stinks worse than Panvel during low tide. A police officer from the city has vanished, leaving behind a letter that names names and accuses a senior official of shady dealings.</p>
<p>The missing cop's wife has ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-corruption.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COVID Outbreak Hits Navi Mumbai School</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/covid-school-nm.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: 18 students at a Navi Mumbai school tested positive for COVID. Remember when we <em>didn't</em> have to worry about this? Good times.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The COVID era isn't quite done with us yet. 18 students at a school in Sector 29, Vashi, tested positive for COVID-19 this week, sending a ripple of anxiety through parents.</p>
<p>The NMMC health department confirmed the cluster on Wednesday. Contact tracing is underway, and the school has been temporari...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/covid-school-nm.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>