<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>The Navi Mumbai Record</title>
        <link>https://navimumbairecord.com</link>
        <description>Navi Mumbai's Authentic News Source</description>
        <item>
            <title>Airport Name Fight: More Protests Coming?</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-name-protest.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: All-party meeting today decides on future protests over the naming of Navi Mumbai Airport. Expect more drama than an Ekta Kapoor serial.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The naming saga of Navi Mumbai International Airport continues, folks. Today's the day political parties huddle to decide whether to unleash more protests. All thanks to the ongoing disagreement over whether it should be named after D.B. Patil.</p>
<p>Remember those massive human chains and shutdown th...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/airport-name-protest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kharghar, Ulwe: No Water This Sunday</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-water-cut.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Water supply is cut off in Kharghar, Ulwe, and Dronagiri this Sunday. Guess it's time to finally visit that weird water park in Belapur. </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Planning on showering this Sunday? You might want to rethink that. NMMC has announced a water supply shutdown affecting Kharghar, Ulwe, and Dronagiri nodes. </p>
<p>The disruption kicks in at 10:00 AM on Sunday, June 9th, and is expected to last until 10:00 AM on Monday, June 10th. Blame the Maharasht...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/kharghar-water-cut.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COVID Hits Nerul School: 18 Students Infected</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/covid-nerul-school.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: 18 students at a Nerul school tested positive for COVID, raising concerns about a new outbreak. This is either a blip or the start of something bigger – place your bets, folks.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>A private school in Nerul's Sector 21 is dealing with a COVID-19 cluster. 18 students have tested positive since last week, forcing the school to shut down temporarily.</p>
<p>The news has parents scrambling. Are we back to online classes and existential dread? O...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/covid-nerul-school.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cop Vanishes; Letter Blames Senior For Graft</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-graft.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A Navi Mumbai police officer is missing after a letter surfaced accusing a superior of corruption. This smells like a bad Bollywood script, but it's real life in khaki.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Navi Mumbai police force has a mystery on its hands. Inspector Abhay Kurundkar is MIA, and things are getting spicy fast. A letter, purportedly penned by Kurundkar himself, alleges rampant corruption within the ranks, directly implicating a senior officer. The letter...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/missing-cop-graft.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Metro Line 1: Smooth Ride Ahead</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-line-trials.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Metro Line 1 oscillation trials are done! Get ready for quicker commutes... eventually.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Metro Line 1 just wrapped up its oscillation trials. Think of it like the metro's final exam before it starts carrying actual people (and hopefully, less pigeons). </p>
<p>The Commissioner of Metro Rail Safety (CMRS) gave the thumbs-up after three days of testing at various speeds. The trial runs were conducted between Pendhar and Belapur, with the C...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-line-trials.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Hanuman Chalisa Heard Loudly Outside Vashi Showroom</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-ad-protest.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Right-wing group protested outside a clothing store in Vashi over an allegedly offensive ad. The vibes were definitely not chill.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>A gaggle of saffron-clad activists from some pro-Hindu group (who can keep track anymore?) descended on a clothing showroom in Vashi Sector 17 this afternoon. Their beef? Apparently, an advertisement offended their delicate sensibilities.</p>
<p>The advertisement, plastered across the store's front window lik...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/vashi-ad-protest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Election Noise: Politicians Ignore Navi Mumbai's Air Quality</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/election-noise-pollution.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Politicians are blasting music and setting off firecrackers during the election, making the already bad air quality even worse. Honestly, do they even live here?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The election season has brought the usual cacophony, but this year, residents are breathing more than just political promises. Loud music and firecrackers have become the soundtrack to campaigning, much to the dismay of anyone trying to, you know, breathe.</p>
<p>One resident v...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/election-noise-pollution.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Student fleeced ₹2 Lakh in Scholarship Scam</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/scholarship-scam.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: A student lost ₹2 lakh, including scholarship money, to cyber fraud. Seriously, people, stop clicking random links! </p>
</blockquote>
<p>Imagine your scholarship money vanishing into thin air. That's exactly what happened to one unlucky student in Kharghar last week. They got scammed out of ₹2 lakh.</p>
<p>The student, whose name is being withheld because, you know, victim-blaming is a thing, clicked on a link promising some kind of scholarship update. Ins...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/scholarship-scam.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Creep Creates Fake Insta, Posts Teen's Dirty Pics</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/insta-creep-arrest.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: Some loser made a fake Instagram account and posted obscene garbage of a teenager. The cyber police finally caught the idiot.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>A Taloja resident is cooling his heels after allegedly creating a fake Instagram account to post vile content featuring a local teen. The Navi Mumbai cyber police arrested the 23-year-old this week, proving that sometimes, justice actually works.</p>
<p>According to the cops, the accused, identified as [REDACTED ...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/insta-creep-arrest.html</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Navi Mumbai Metro: Trial Run SUCCESS!</title>
            <link>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trial-success.html</link>
            <description><blockquote>
<p><strong>TLDR</strong>: CIDCO's metro line is closer than ever after a successful trial run. Finally, something actually works in this city.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The Navi Mumbai Metro chugged along its Pendhar to Central Park route today for a successful trial run. Finally, after what feels like a decade of delays, Sector 14 might actually be accessible. </p>
<p>CIDCO officials confirmed the train smoothly navigated the 11-km stretch. The grey line promises to link Panvel to Belap...</description>
            <pubDate>2026-01-11</pubDate>
            <guid>https://navimumbairecord.com/news/2026-01-11/metro-trial-success.html</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>